Guide to the Child Study Center, School of Medicine, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Donald J. Cohen as director, circa 1983-2001; Accession 2003-A-024
  - Pro-Neuron Meeting, January 20, 1998, HOPE 212 (Box 26)
  - Center for Jewish History. Sunday, October 1, 1995, 11:00AM, New York City (Box 26)
  - Pet Center (Box 26)
  - Police (Box 26)
  - Conn. Law Enforcement Crime Prevention Association, July 8, 1992 10: am (Box 26)
  - N.H. Police Referrals to CSC (Box 26)
  - CSC/Police Department Correspondence (Box 26)
  - Child Development Community Policing Program (Box 26)
  - Chief Nicholas Pastore (Box 26)
  - Child Development and Community Policing, May 10, 1993, Yale University Campus, New Haven, Connecticut (Box 26)
  - City Live ability Awards Program (Box 26)
  - McLean Hospital, April 6, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Grover Powers Clinic, Dr. R Granger (Box 27)
  - Barry Prizant, PhD. Seminar, July 20, 1988, 4:00 PM, Senn Conference Rm. (Box 27)
  - Project Hope (Box 27)
  - Department of Psychology (Box 27)
  - Faculty-Materials (Box 27)
  - Psychology Department Agreement (Box 27)
  - Psychology Department Clinic (Box 27)
  - Psychology Fellows (Box 27)
  - School Year Materials (Box 27)
  - Psychology Search Committee (Box 27)
  - Psychology, Child Psychiatry, 671a,b/Psychiatry (Box 27)
  - PGY Residents: 1991-1992 (Box 27)
  - PGY II 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Child Psychiatry 671 a,b Psychology Teaching 1991-1992 (Box 27)
  - PGY II 1989-1990 (Box 27)
  - Child Psychiatry in General Psychiatry Syllabus (Box 27)
  - Course Form (Box 27)
  - PGY II Seminar, 1985-1986 (Box 27)
  - Residents: PGY II, III, IV, V, Seminar Schedule 1983-84 (Box 27)
  - PG-2 Courses 1985-86 (Box 27)
  - PGY II Seminar, Child Psychiatry and Personality Development, October-May 1984-1985 (Box 27)
  - June 3, 1991, Child Analysis Meeting, Senn Conference Room 5:15 pm (Box 27)
  - Oedipal Minds (Box 27)
  - "R' Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Commissioner Audrey Rowe, February 8, 1994, 9:00 AM, Hartford (Box 27)
  - Renaissance Fellowship Program (Box 27)
  - REF (Request for Proposals) Child Development (Box 27)
  - Rehabilitation, Research and Training Centers (RRTC) (Box 27)
  - Recommendation Letters (A-L) (Box 27)
  - Recommendation Letters (M-Z) (Box 27)
  - Rabbi Riskin (Box 28)
  - Riverview Board (Box 28)
  - Sachem Forensic Unit at Riverview Hospital for Children and Youth (Box 28)
  - Riverview Hospital (Box 28)
  - Riverview Hospital Correspondence (Box 28)
  - Riverview Advisory Board Meeting (Box 28)
  - Connecticut Valley Hospital Residence Program (Box 28)
  - Riverview Board Meeting, July 17, 1995, 8:30-10:00 AM (Box 28)
  - Riverview Hospital (Box 28)
  - `Rogers, Fred Mr., Family Communications, Inc., Pittsburgh Pennsylvania (Box 28)
  - The Leon E.. Rosenberg Portrait Committee (Box 28)
  - Office of the Dean (Box 28)
  - Rosoff, Mr. Saul, Director, Office of Child Development (Box 28)
  - Saul Rosoff Dinner, Cosmos Club, Washington, DC., October 3, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Rosoff, Saul, Paris Trip (Box 28)
  - Roth and Moore (Box 29)
  - Russia (Box 29)
  - Russian Correspondence (Box 29)
  - "S" Miscellaneous I (Box 29)
  - "S" Miscellaneous II (Box 29)
  - "S" Miscellaneous III (Box 29)
  - Shuttle Crises (Box 29)
  - SAHA International (Box 29)
  - Samsung, December 16, 1996 (Box 29)
  - Allan B. Schwartz Productions (Box 29)
  - Singapore (Box 29)
  - 60 minutes, May 18th, 2000. 2:30-4:30 PM (Box 29)
  - Mikle South (Box 29)
  - Spark (Box 29)
  - Stop Crime, give Kids a Chance, Advisory Committee (Box 29)
  - Sackler School of Medicine and CSC Exchange Program (Box 29)
  - Safe Schools (Box 29)
  - Keynote Address: New Haven Family Alliance, May 2, 1994 12:00 PM (Box 29)
  - Anne-Marie Sandler, Visit to CSC, April 12, 1993 (Box 29)
  - International Newsletter on Autism: Sanua, Victor D. (Box 29)
  - Saudi Arabia (Box 30)
  - Saved the Children (Box 30)
  - Robert Wood Johnson, Evaluation of Mental Health Services (Box 30)
  - RWJ Project at Brandeis, June 4, 1992 (Box 30)
  - Robert Wood Johnson (Box 30)
  - Mental health Services, Brandies-Heller School, Leonard Saxe, PhD., September 12, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Schmidt, Benno (Box 30)
  - President's Tea, Februaty 18, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Shalit/Schneider, August 16, 1999, 9:00 AM (Box 30)
  - Schneider Children's Medical Center of Israel (Box 30)
  - The Feinbergs (Lectures) (Box 30)
  - School Intervention Minutes (Box 30)
  - Schopler, Eric (Box 30)
  - School Intervention Team Thursday, December 21, 1995, 11:00 AM (Box 30)
  - School Based Crises Intervention Committee, David Schonfeld, MD (Box 30)
  - Secretin (Box 30)
  - Senatorial List (Box 30)
  - Senn Memorial Service, September 17, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Sesame Street for Israel, Palestine and Jordan, Brainstorming Session, April 24, 2001 (Box 30)
  - Sexual Harassment (Box 31)
  - Columbia University, MHCRC (Box 31)
  - Australia, TS Conference, May 1995 (Box 31)
  - TS Medications, Treatment (Box 31)
  - Tourette Syndrome Symposium, Oslo, Norway (Box 31)
  - TSA Association Bayside, New York, September 12-13, 1992 (Box 31)
  - TS Group List (Box 31)
  - TSA: 8thGenetic Workshop (Box 31)
  - Tourette Syndrome Genetics Meeting, March 26-27, 1992, Cambridge, Massachusetts (Box 31)
  - Tourette Syndrome: Report Seventh Genetic Workshop, June 15, 1991, Boston, MA (Box 31)
  - Tourette Syndrome in Israel (Box 31)
  - Second International Scientific Symposium on TS, Boston, MA, June 16-18, 1991 (Box 31)
  - Tourette Syndrome Association 3rdInternational Symposium (Blue Folder), Also contains Advertisements, Faxes, General Correspondence, E-Mails, Grants, Letter of Acceptance, Letter of invitation Scientific Advisory Committee (Box 31)
  - Tourette Syndrome Association (Box 31)
  - TS Articles/Newspaper Other Papers (Box 31)
  - A Guide to TS (Box 31)
  - TSA Insurance Face Sheet (Box 31)
  - Diagnostic Procedures for the TSA Genetics Consortium (Box 31)
  - TSA Scientific Advisory Board (Box 31)
  - TSA Medical Committee (Box 31)
  - TSA International Planning Meeting, Washington, DC, December 18-19, 1989 (Box 31)
  - TSA: Task Force on Residential Needs (Box 31)
  - TSA/CSC Agreement May 1988 (Box 31)
  - TS Workshop on Definitions of Tic Disorders (Box 31)
  - First International/Tourette Syndrome Conference, May 27-29, 1981 (Box 31)
  - International Tourette Syndrome Meeting. Paris, France, May 2-3 1985 (Box 31)
  - TS Conference: Israel, June, 87 (Box 31)
  - American/Israel Collaboration Tourette Syndrome Association, Jan 22-29 (Box 31)
  - Tourette Syndrome Association., Ohio (Box 31)
  - TS/OCD Program Project (Box 31)
  - TS Program Project Grant (Box 32)
  - TS Program Project (Box 32)
  - Trauma Book (Box 32)
  - Conference Grant Applications (Box 32)
  - Summerbridge (Box 32)
  - Surgeon General's Report on Mental Health, 1999 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous "T" (Box 32)
  - TS Program Project (Box 32)
  - Tel Aviv Mental Health Clinic (Box 32)
  - Tel Aviv University (Box 32)
  - SOI: Science, Law and Social Policy Advisory committee Friday, Sept. 29, 1995, 3:00-5:00 PM (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, Science, Law, Social Policy, March 9, 1995. (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics Science, Law And Social Policy Comm. July 6, 1994. (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, World Games Connecticut 1995. (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, International 1995 (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, Press Conference June 26, 1995 (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, Law School Faculty (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, Office of Science and Social Policy, Minutes: April 28, 1994 Meeting (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, Social Policy Committee (Box 33)
  - 1995, Special Olympics, World Games, Wednesday, January 18, 1995 3:00-5:00PM, Senn Conference Room I-271 (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, December 10, 1993 Dome Room (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, Science and Social Policy Committee, January 19, 1994 (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, September 22, 1993 (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, Meeting April 27, 1993 CSC (Box 33)
  - Interroburst IV, April 23-24, 1993, Special Olympics (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics, 1995, World Summer Games November 19, 1995, Hartford. (Box 33)
  - Special Olympics 25thAnniversary (1968-1993) (Box 33)
  - Classification of Tics, DSM-3-R (Box 33)
  - DSM-III Meeting, New York, Psychiatric Institute, September 23, 1985 (Box 33)
  - Spitzer, Robert L., MD, Chairman, APA Task Force on Nomenclature and Statistics (DSM-III) (Box 33)
  - Spitzer Meeting, New York City, February 27, 1985 (Box 33)
  - Tourette Syndrome Meeting, New York City, April 2-3, 1985 (Box 33)
  - Clark Springgate, MD., PhD. Springgate Associates, Biopharmaceutical Consulting (Box 33)
  - Stahl, Stephen M., MD, University of Chicago (Box 33)
  - State of Connecticut (Box 33)
  - SLLF Conference, March 5-7, 1993 (Box 33)
  - UMBC, The Shriver Center, National Advisory Board, April 28, 1998 (Hard Cover Folder) (Box 34)
  - Singer, Jerome, Professor of Clinical Psychology, Yale University School Of Medicine (Box 34)
  - Solnit Professorship (Box 34)
  - Southbury Training School (Box 34)
  - Special Olympics: 1995, World Summer Games (Box 34)
  - Press Conference, June 12, 1995 (Box 34)
  - Massachusetts Mutual (Box 34)
  - Massachusetts Mutual Meeting Mory's, Thursday, February 2, 1989 (Box 34)
  - AACP Meeting, October 21-25, 1987 (Box 34)
  - Child Advocate Class, November 29, 1984 2:10-4:00 PM (Box 34)
  - World Psychiatric Association, Traumatic Conference, November 16-21, 1997, Jerusalem, Israel (Box 34)
  - World Federation of Societies of Biological Psychiatry (WFSBP), Jerusalem, April 2-7, 1989 Correspondence (Box 35)
  - World Fed Abstracts (Box 35)
  - U.V, W,X, Y, Z Miscellaneous (Box 35)
  - Testimony to the Commission on Hospital and Health Care on the Certificate of Need (Box 35)
  - Certificate of Need Testimony, Donald J. Cohen, MD (Box 35)
  - Certificate of Need Questions and Answers (Box 35)
  - Certificate of Need Meeting, March 15, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Certificate of Need (Box 35)
  - Certificate of Need Hearing 11/28/83 (Box 35)
  - Weisswasser Lecture, Ruth Stein, MD, April 7, 1999 (Box 35)
  - Warren Weisswasser Gifts (Box 35)
  - Weisswasser Lecture, February 13-14, 1996 (Box 35)
  - Warren Weiswasser Lecture. Speaker: Jack Shonkoff, MD. Grand Rounds: Wednesday March 8, 1995 (Box 35)
  - Warren Weiswasser Lecture, 1/27/93 (Box 35)
  - The Welch Center (Box 35)
  - Working Group on Welfare Reform, Family Support and Independence (Box 35)
  - West Haven Mental Health Center, Marc Rubenstein (Box 35)
  - Wneip, Human Development Course (Box 35)
  - Western New England Site Visit, February -26 March 1, 1992 (Box 35)
  - WNEIP Symposium, April 17, 1993 (Box 35)
  - WNEIP: Education Committee Meeting, Thursday, 11 February 1993, 6:30 PM (Box 36)
  - General Correspondence (Box 36)
  - Membership (Box 36)
  - Kathy Wilcox correspondence (Box 36)
  - WNEIP class (Box 36)
  - WNEIP-1992 Human Development (Box 36)
  - Tunney, John V., U.S. Senator, California (Box 36)
  - Frank Turner, Provost (Box 36)
  - Vaccine/ Austism Release (Box 36)
  - University of Utah Health System. A. Lorris Betz, MD, Ph. D (Box 36)
  - U Conn Health Initiation (Box 36)
  - Dept of Health and Human Services, Mental Health service Use, Need, Outcomes, and Costs in Child and Adolescent Population (Box 36)
  - UNO/CSC (Box 36)
  - UNO-CAP Meeting December 12/21/94 9:30 -12:00 PM, Donald J. Cohen's Office (Box 36)
  - Urban Affairs Conference, December 12, 1992 (Box 36)
  - `Urban Education Fellowship (Box 36)
  - U. S. House of Representatives (Box 36)
  - United Way (Box 36)
  - CSC: Visiting Professor, Application (Box 36)
  - Letter of Encouragement (Box 36)
  - Letter of Discouragement (Box 36)
  - Visiting Professor Refusal (Box 36)
  - CSC: Visiting Scholars Misc. (Box 36)
  - Miscellaneous Students (Box 36)
  - Weisswasser Lecture, March 28, 2001 (Box 36)
  - Warner Brothers, Autism Film (Box 36)
  - Wilbur Cross High School (Box 36)
  - Wilbur Cross Day Care Center (Box 36)
  - Stanley Walzer, MD, Visit: December 12-13, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Children's Day May 10-11, 1991, Department of Pediatrics (Box 36)
- Child Study films, circa 1960-1975; Accession 2004-A-064
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - #10 Make Believe, play film;--sound and picture, 2 (Box 1)
  - #11 Play school -pretend meal and more play;--sound and picture, 2 (Box 2)
  - #12 Make Believe, play film; fim reel (16mm)--sound (Box 3)
  - #7 Playroom: doctor -nurse segment,--sound and picture, 2 (Box 4)
  - #8 Make Believe, play film;--sound and picture, 2 (Box 5)
  - #3 Make Believe, play film;--sound and picture, 2 (Box 6)
  - #6 Children at day care,--sound and picture, 2 (Box 7)
  - #5 Make Believe, play film;--sound and picture, 2 (Box 8)
  - #9 Make Believe, play film;--sound and picture, 2 (Box 9)
  - #4 Children at day care,--sound and picture, 2 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified, 1 (Box 11)
  - Unidentified, 1 (Box 12)
  - Unidentified, 1 (Box 13)
  - Unidentified, 1 (Box 14)
  - Unidentified, 1 (Box 15)
  - #13 Piano and vocals,--sound, 1 (Box 16)
- Records of Donald J. Cohen as director, 1976-2001; Accession 2008-A-099
  - WHITE HOUSE -CONFERENCE EARLY CHILDHOOD DEVELOPMENT, 1997 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - WHITE HOUSE -CONFERENCE "THE PSYCHOBILOGY OF DEVELOPMENT: BRAIN, BEHAVIOR, AND CARE", 1997 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - BAR ILAN UNIVERSITY HONORARY DEGREE PRESENTATION ISRAEL, 1997 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - BAR ILAN UNIVERSITY HONORARY DEGREE ACCEPTANCE ISRAEL, 1997 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - TSA DINNER - LOS ANGELES, 2001 February (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - TSA SPEECH - LOS ANGELES, 2001 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - RUANE AWARD NARSAD RESEARCH, 2000 October 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AMERICAN PSYCHIATRIC TOS. - SPECIAL PRESIDENTIAL COMMENDATION, 2001 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - THE PROMISED CHILDHOOD, 2001 April (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - JERUSALEM, 2001 April (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - STERLING LECTURE, 2001 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - SCHNEIDER CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL ISRAEL, 1999 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - IACAPAP-STOCKHOLM PRESIDENTIAL LECTURE and MENTAL HEALTH SYSTEMS FOR CHILDREN AND ADOLESCENTS, 1998 August (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - MARIANNE KRIS LECTURE "DRAFT", 1998 April (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 3 computer files (DOC)
  - AMERICAN ACADEMY MEETING TORONTO, CANADA SYMPOSIUM ON MDD, 1997 October (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - computer file (DOC)
  - TELEFON AZURO, ROME, ITALY, 1997 June (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - LAWYERS FOR CHILDREN STEVEN MARANS, 1997 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 3 computer files (DOC)
  - D.J. COHEN BIOGRAPHIC STATEMENT, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - BIO-SKETCH FORMS, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - WESTERN NEW ENGLAND CONTINOUS CASE III, 1999 January-March (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - WNEIP TECHNIQUES II, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 12 computer files (DOC, WPD)
  - CSC ADMINISTRATIVE TEAM MEMOS AND MINUTES, 1988 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - CSC TEAM MEETING, 1984 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - CSC FACULTY RETREAT, 2000 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CHILD PSYCHIATRY CLERKSHIP, 1992 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - CHILD PSYCHIATRY/ER, 1993 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - CSC: OUTPATIENT CLINIC FEES, 1990 January 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - CSC: MEETING OF THE BOARD, 1989 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - OPENING MEETING, 2000 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - OPENING MEETING, 1996 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - CHILD STUDY CENTER OPENING MEETING, 1995 September 5 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - OPENING MEETING, 1994 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - OPENING MEETING, 1992 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - WELCOME MEETING, 1993 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - WELCOME BREAKFAST, 1990 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - OPENING MEETING, 1991 September 3 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - OPENING MEETING, 1988 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - OPENING MEETING, 1987 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - OPENING MEETING, 1986 September 2 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - CSC DESCRIPTION, circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - C and T ISSUES, 1995 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - SALARY MEETING, 1991 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - FACULTY MEETING SALARY APPOINTMENTS, 1990 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - CSC: PERSONNEL SALARY ADJUSTMENTS, 1981 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - DEDICATION, NEW WING, CSC, 1977 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - CSC INTERNATIONAL YEAR OF THE CHILD, 1979 June 21-23 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - CSC HISTORY, circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - CSC HISTORY - FIRST DRAFT (ORIGINAL), circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - CHILD STUDY CENTER PUBLICITY, circa 1990 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - CSC: SPACE, circa 1990 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - CSC: FIVE YEAR SITE-VISIT, 1988 February 4-5 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - CSC: PROJECTS and PROGRAMS J. WILKINSON, 1984 March 7 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - NEWSPAPER ARTICLES ABOUT CHILDREN AND CITY VIOLENCE, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - FAMILY: THIRD ANNUAL SENATE PRESIDENT'S CONFERENCE LEGISLATIVE OFFICE BUILDING HARTFORD, 1990 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - AUTISM: DIAGNOSIS, ASSESSMENT AND INTERVENTION, 1990 July 24 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - CLINICAL CARE and THE SETTING FOR THE STUDY OF DEVELOPMENTAL PSYCHOPATHOLOGY NICHD, 1989 June (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - TOURETTE SYNDROME ASSOCIATION MCLEAN, VIRGINIA, 1989 November 11 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - CLINICAL RESEARCH and THE CARE OF CHILDREN: 25 YEARS OF CHILD PSYCHIATRY and THE NEXT DECADE OR TWO. TUFTS MED. CENTER, 1989 November 2 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - ARTHUR Z. MUTTER, M.D. NEW ENGLAND MEDICAL CENTER TUFTS UNIVERSITY, 1989 November 2 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - TOURETTE'S SYNDROME: A MODEL DISORDER FOR INTEGRATING PSYCHOANALYTICAL and BIOLOGICAL PERSPECTIVES. LONDON, 1989 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - CLINICAL CARE AS THE SETTING FOR THE STUDY OF DEVELOPMENTAL PSYCHOPATHOLOGY: NICHD BETHESDA, MD, 1989 June (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - INTRODUCTION TO CONFERENCE ON MENTAL HEALTH ASSESSMENT AND SERVICES IN PRIMARY HEALTH SETTINGS, PARK PLAZA, 1989 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - OPENING AND CLOSING COMMENTS: NAT'L. MENTAL HEALTH ASSOC. AND THE 101ST CONGRESS, WASHINGTON, DC, 1989 June 8 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - PSYCHOPHARMACOLOGY and THE CLINICAL CARE OF CHILDREN and ADOLESCENTS: TS AS A MODEL JAYCEE NEUROPSYCHIATRIC CTR. HARTFORD, 1989 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - PRESENTATION SPEECH FOR JIM COMER: HELPING HANDS DINNER, 1989 April 18 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - CHARACTER, AGRESSION and FANTASY: PSYCHOANALYTIC STUDIES OF CHILDREN and ADULTS ISRAEL SOCIETY OF PSYCHO. JERUSALEM, 1989 March 30 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - DEVELOPMENTAL PSYCHOPATHOLOGY EMERGING PARADIGMS FOR RESEARCH ON PSYCHIATRIC DISORDERS OF CHILDHOOD: ISRAEL SOCIETY OF CHILD and ADOLESC. PSYCHIATRY, JERUSALEM, 1989 March 29 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - INSTITUTE OF PSYCHIATRY LONDON, 1989 March 3 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL - GRAND ROUNDS BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS, 1989 February 15 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - CHARACTER, AGRESSION AND FANTASY: PSYCHOANALYTIC STUDIES OF CHILDREN AND ADULTS, 1988 November 17 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - HILLSIDE HOSPITAL GRAND ROUNDS NEW YORK, NEW YORK "AUTISM and DEVELOPMENTAL DISORDERS", 1988 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - CSC CONFERENCE: CLINICAL RESEARCH and CLINICAL CARE, 1988 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - BRANDEIS ALUMNI MEETING SPEECH, 1988 June 23 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - CHILD AND ADOLESDCENT MENTAL HEALTH: NEUROBIOLOGICAL and SOCIAL KNOWLEDGE AND THEIR APPLICATION FOR CHILDREN AND FAMILIES, NY ACADEMY OF MED., 1988 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - THE NEUROPSYCHIATRIC DISORDERS OF CHILDHOOD: UNDERSTANDING THE NEEDS OF THE INDIVIDUAL CHILD. SAPPORO, JAPAN, 1988 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - INTRODUCTION TO ASSESSMENT CONFERENCE, 1988 March 25 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - DISCUSSION OF PRESENTATION BY STANLEY LEAVY, M.D.: "REALITY IN RELIGION and PSYCHOANALYSIS" WNEIP, 1988 March 12 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - "MIND AND BODY" TV SHOW PRINCETON, NEW JERSEY, 1988 March 10-11 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - ASSOCIATES PRESENTATION, 1987 November 19 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - PLAY IN THE OEDIPAL PHASE AND ADULTHOOD PRESENTATION: CSC, 1987 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - FINDING MEANING IN OTHERS: BEHAVIORAL and BIOLOGICAL STUDIES OF SERIOUS CHILDHOOD PSYCHOPATH. MAURICE W. LAUFER LECTURE BROWN UNIV. PROVIDENCE, 1987 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - BENHAVEN 20TH ANNIVERSARY OCTOBER 1987 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - BEHAVIORAL AND BIOLOGICAL STUDIES OF AUTISM, 1987 April (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - INTRODUCTION: CLIFFORD BEERS LECTURE, 1987 March 24 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - NIMH ELEANOR DIBBLE, 1987 February 20 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - PLAYING and THERAPEUTIC ACTION IN CHILD ANALYSIS, 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - CSC: 75THANNIVERSARY CELEBRATION, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - AUDITORS REPORT, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - AUDIT CHILD STUDY CENTER, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - CSC AUDIT, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - ADMINISTRATIVE STATUS, CHILD STUDY CENTER, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - CSC COMPLIANCE AUDIT PROGRESS, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - GSC ADMINISTRATIVE TEAM, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - COMMENTS DC, 1990, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - TRAUMA AND ADAPTATION. MEXICAN SOCIETY OF CHILD and ADOLESCENT PSYCHIATRY, MEXICO CITY, 1996 February 22 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - NEUROPSYCHIATRIC DISORDERS OF CHILDHOOD: TS AS A MODEL, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - VU;MERAN;E CJO;D: OMTERMAL EFFECTS OF CHRONIC VS. SHORT-TERM TRAUMA IN CHILDHOOD, APA MEETING, DECEMBER, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - THE INSTITUTE OF LIVING 4THANNUAL BEN WIESEL LECTURESHIP, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - JOSEPH SLIFKA CENTER DEDICATION, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - ETHICAL ASPECTS OF RESEARCH ON CHILDREN, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE UNDERSTANDING YOUTH SUICIDE: A MEETING OF DIFFERENCE PERSPECTIVES, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - CHILDHOOD DEPRESSION, UNIVERSITY OF ALEXANDRIA, 1995 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - UN SYMPOSIUM, 1995 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - SPECIAL OLYMPICS, UNITED NATIONS SYMPOSIUM, 1995 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - PRESS CONFERENCE NICHD, 1995 June 26 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - BIOMEDICAL RESEARCH and HEALTH: PREVENTION, EARLY INTERVENTION AND TREATMENT OF INDIVIDUALS WITH MENTAL RETARDATION, UNITED NATIONS SYMPOSIUM, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - ADOLESENCE TODAY: ISRAELI YOUTH RELATIVE TO WESTERN TRENDS, THE VAN LEER FORUM, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - DEVELOPMENTAL PSYCHOPATHOLOGY OF CHILD AND ADOLESCENT PSYCHIATRIC DISORDERS, 1995 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - SPEAKER OF THE HOUSE, HARTFORD, CONNECTICUT, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - PEDIATRIC PSYCHOPHARMACOLOGY IN CHILDREN AND ADOLESCENTS, NIHM, WASHINGTON, 1995 January 24-25 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - TORUETTE'S SYNDROME AS A MODEL, GENETICALLY TRANSMITTED NEUROPSYCHIATRIC DISORDER, PRINCETON, 1995 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - CHILD and ADOLESCENT PHSCHIATRY IN THE FUTURE: DELIVERING EFFECTIVE CARE, CENTER FOR ADVANCED STUDY IN BEHAVIORAL SCIENCES, 1995 January 1 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - AUTISM: THE PRECONDITIONS OF DEVELOPMENT AND THE PHENOMENOLOGY OF LOVING, 1994 September 13 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - CHILD PSYCHIATRISTS AT THE FRONT: CHILDREN'S ADAPTIONS TO WAR AND U RBAN TRAUMA, AACAP, 1994 October 24-29 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL 155TH CELEBRATION, 1994 June 9-11 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - 13TH CONGRESS OF IACAPAP PRESIDENTIAL LECTURE, 1994 July 24-28 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - RESEARCH IN SCHOOL REFORM: THE CO MER SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM AT 25, 1994 May 9 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - CONCEPTUALIZING BOARDERLINE SYNDROME OF CHILDHOOD AND CHILDHOOD SCHIZOPHDRENIA AS A DEVELOPMENTAL DISORDER, ALBERT EINSTEIN MED. SCHOOL, 1994 May 12 (Box 3, Folder 123)